vidaselect.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy

VIDA LLC ("VIDA") created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our strong commitment to helping Users and Clients better understand what information we collect about them and what may happen to that information.

**Overview**  
By accepting this Privacy Policy and VIDA’s Terms and Conditions, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the VIDA Terms and Conditions.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for [https://www.vidaselect.com](https://www.vidaselect.com/).

This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Minors (under 18) are not eligible to use our services**  
Children are not eligible to use our services, and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Privacy and Use of Information**  
VIDA will use the User’s personal data to provide our services e.g. processing payments or to send the User service-related messages such as confirmation emails and other messages concerning his/her relationship with VIDA. We also use the personal data the Client provides us to build dating profiles that will be created on a number of third party dating websites. This data will be available to the Client at any point.

VIDA will use the User’s personal data to help us communicate with effectively should he/she try to contact us via our site including verification of any claims he/she may make.

VIDA may use cookies, IP addresses or personal data to recognize the User when he/she visit or return to our Website so we can show the User ads or other content tailored to the User’s preferences, to track anonymous traffic, demographic and usage patterns, to prevent or detect fraud or abuses or to help us improve our website.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

VIDA may access, monitor, remove, alter or store or otherwise use any personal data if we think the User has or may have breached our Terms and Conditions or to enforce our rights or protect the public or where if we are required to do so by law or appropriate authority.

VIDA is not responsible and cannot control the use of information provided by a User to a third party, and will not be held liable for same.

The User may not use the Website or Services for any unlawful purpose. Should the User use the Website and Services for any unlawful purpose, VIDA will relay all information to law enforcement services in the appropriate jurisdiction. VIDA will refuse to register a User, should that User be impersonating another party or is protected by trademark or copyright law.

VIDA does not and will not disclose any personal information of a User that a User does not wish to be disclosed to any third party by VIDA.

VIDA understands the importance of strict confidentiality. Hence, VIDA, unless the User agrees to otherwise in the course of using the service, agrees to keep all information provided by the User, including personal information strictly confidential.

VIDA will only commence communications with a potential match with the expressed permission and approval of the Client. Any personal information provided (e.g., personal email, telephone number) to an approved match will be with the expressed permission of the Client. Under no circumstances, unless ordered by law or agreed upon by the Client, will Virtual Dating Assistance disclose the name and contact information of the Client to third parties not related to the provision of the service. Further, VIDA will not under any circumstance disclose to any matches the Client’s use of VIDA’s services.

The User acknowledges and agrees to VIDA disclosing any information the User provides if required or permitted to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if VIDA, in its sole discretion believes that such disclosure is reasonable to comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement or any legal process, protect or defend VIDA's or a third party's right or to protect someone's life, health or safety, at such point when harm or violence against any person including the User is threatened.

Notwithstanding any other provision or condition contained herein or VIDA’s Privacy Policy contained on the Website, VIDA reserves the right, to disclose any or all information that is submitted by a User to VIDA. Should VIDA believe or has reason to believe that the information involves a party who may be a victim of abuse in any form. Abuse is hereinafter defined as spousal abuse, elder abuse, child abuse or domestic violence. The User hereby acknowledges and agrees to hold and save harmless VIDA from any and all claims or third party claims that may arise. VIDA may, at its sole discretion, disclose information to authorities that VIDA deems to be appropriate to handle such disclosure. The User hereby acknowledges and agrees that VIDA is permitted to make such a disclosure.

The User hereby acknowledges and agrees that VIDA may and can use anonymized information from the User in respect of the User's experiences through use of the Website and Services for relationship research purposes.

Any advice or opinions or statements made available through the Website or Services, are those of the author and should not be necessarily relied upon.

**Security**  
Security is a high priority. VIDA takes precautions to protect personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction using the same safeguards as we use for our own proprietary information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Cookies**  
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Use of VidaSelect.com**  
All participants and visitors fully understand that unless VIDA clearly identifies itself as being the owner or supplier of the information, VIDA does not have control or endorse any other products not related to our website in any other way, except for identified information, products or services, all information, products and services offered through the website or on the Internet generally are offered by third parties, that are not affiliated with VIDA. Visitors and participants understand that we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading through our website will be free of infection or viruses, worms, Trojan horses or other code that manifest contaminating or destructive properties. You will be responsible for implementing procedures to satisfy your particular requirements for the accuracy of data input and output on our website. All Visitors to this site assume complete responsibility for the use of this website and the internet. VIDA provides this website and its related information as “as is” and we do not make any warranties, endorsements or representations whatsoever. Including without limitation warranties of title or non-infringement, or the warranties of merchantability for a particular purpose, in regards to the service, any merchandise information or service provided through the service or on the internet generally, and VIDA will not be liable for any costs or damages arising either directly or indirectly from any such transaction. It is completely your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness and usefulness of all opinions, advice, services, merchandise and other information provided through the service on the internet in general. VIDA does not guarantee or warrant that these services will be error-free or uninterrupted or the defects in the service will be fixed or addressed.

**Registration**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.

**Notice**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes shall be in effect immediately once made to the website. The User's continued use of the Website and/or Services, after the posting of amendments to this Privacy Policy, will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such amendments, modifications, additions or deletions. The User hereby agrees to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be aware of any such amendments or modifications.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-877-271-1717 or via [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#274448495346445367514e434654424b4244530944484a).

**Revision Date**  
This Policy was last revised on May 5, 2017  
Copyright © 2019 VIDA LLC
